{
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": 0,
            "question": "Od slova 'by':",
            "options": [
                "aby",
                "čoby"
            ],
            "correctOption": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Od slova 'býk':",
            "options": [
                "býček",
                "býkovec"
            ],
            "correctOption": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "Od slova 'byľ':",
            "options": [
                "byľka",
                "bylinkový",
                "bylina"
            ],
            "correctOption": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "Od slova 'bystrý':",
            "options": [
                "bystriť",
                "bystro"
            ],
            "correctOption": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "Od slova 'Bytča':",
            "options": [
                "Bytčan",
                "bytčianský"
            ],
            "correctOption": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "Od slova 'byť':",
            "options": [
                "bytie",
                "bývať"
            ],
            "correctOption": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "Od slova 'bývať':",
            "options": [
                "bytový",
                "bývanie"
            ],
            "correctOption": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "Od slova 'byvol':",
            "options": [
                "byvolí",
                "byvolie"
            ],
            "correctOption": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "Od slova 'bydlo':",
            "options": [
                "obydlie",
                "obytný"
            ],
            "correctOption": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "Od slova 'dobyť':",
            "options": [
                "dobývať",
                "vydobyť"
            ],
            "correctOption": 1
        }
    ]
}
